Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Audio
  - Smith, Tom
    - Songs by Tom Smith, 1990; Notes: "This is a Private Tape for Promotional Use Only, Please buy Commercially-Available Tapes" Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Smith, Tom; Tape
    - Tom Smith Live - 2, Notes: Origin:; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Smith, Tom; Tape - Home recorded cassette
    - Tape 4, Tom Smith (Cont), Notes: Origin:; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
    - The Tom Smith Video Companion ConFusion - 1/21/1989 OVFF IV - 10/29/1988 ConText - 11/19/1988 VHS > VHS > DVD, 1988-1989; Notes: From three different cons Origin: Tim Ryan; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Smith, Tom; Tim Ryan; Burnt DVD
    - Old FUMP Guy: Songs of the FUMP Vol. 3, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Smith, Tom; Burnt CD
    - Sounds Familiar, Vol. 1 OVFF 2011 Preview, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - For Your Confustication, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
    - Who Let Him In Here, 1991; Notes: DR-10002 Origin: Dodeka Records; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Smith, Tom; Dodeka Records; Professional Cassette
    - Domino Death, 1994; Notes: DR-10009 Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Smith, Tom; Professional Cassette
    - Plugged, 1997; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
    - Who Let Him In Here?, 1991; Notes: DR-10002 Origin: Dodeka Records; Professional Cassette 5 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
    - Who Let Him In Here? [home copy], 1991; Notes: DR-10002 Origin: Dodeka Records; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Smith, Tom; Dodeka Records; Tape
  - Snyder, W. Scott
    - Rock and Roll to Hit, 2015; Notes: Origin: Mystic Fig Studios; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Snyder, W. Scott; Mystic Fig Studios; Commercial CD
  - Spears, Lee / Deane, Christopher
    - Confluence, 1985; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Spears, Lee / Deane, Christopher; Professional Cassette
  - Spiner, Brent
    - Brent Spiner - "Ol Yellow Eyes is Back", Notes: Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Spiner, Brent; Tape
  - Starlight
    - Starlight, 2011; Notes: Glover, Rich, Weippert, Stephanie, Gray, John, Radziewicz, Deb, Hagen, Nick, Gray, Alisa Origin: recorded at dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments 19106 DesMoines Mem. Drive, SeaTac,WA 98148; Commercial CD 1 copy; Glover, Rich, Weippert, Stephanie, Gray, John, Radziewicz, Deb, Hagen, Nick, Gray, Alisa; recorded at dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments 19106 DesMoines Mem. Drive, SeaTac,WA 98148 (Box Box #05 (J))
      Glover, Rich, Weippert, Stephanie, Gray, John, Radziewicz, Deb, Hagen, Nick, Gray, Alisa; Starlight; recorded at dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments 19106 DesMoines Mem. Drive, SeaTac,WA 98148; recorded at dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments 19106 DesMoines Mem. Drive, SeaTac,WA 98148; Commercial CD
    - Starlight, 2011; Notes: Starlight comprises Glover, Richard, Weippert, Stephanie, Gray, John, Radziewicz, Deb, Hagen, Nick, Gray, Alisa Origin: dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Starlight; dAigle Autoharps & Folk Instruments; Professional CD
  - Stateman, Howard
    - Howeird's Grossest Hits, 2009; Notes: Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Stateman, Howard; Commercial CD
  - Stevens, Beth
    - Lady of Lies, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Stevens, Beth; Professional Cassette
    - Lady of Lies [unsealed], 1986; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
  - Stevenson, Jean L.
    - Songs for StarVoyagers, 1985; Notes: Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Stevenson, Jean L.; Tape
    - Songs for Starvoyagers, 1985; Notes: professional liner notes, but home recording tape Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Stevenson, Jean L.; Professional Cassette
  - Stranger Ways
    - Strangers at the Gate, 2011; Notes: Includes a note about bonus materials on the website. Origin: Recorded mixed and mastered by the band; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Stranger Ways; Recorded mixed and mastered by the band; Professional CD
    - Guilt, Angst & Fairy Tales, 2012; Notes: Some tracks recorded live at 6PiCon Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Stranger Ways; Commercial CD
  - Sucharikul, Somtow
    - Music of the Rainbow King, 1984; Notes: OCP-25 Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Sucharikul, Somtow; Professional Cassette
  - Sudden Death
    - Dead Things Can Rap Too, 1991; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Sudden Death; Professional Cassette
    - Noise Pollution, 1993; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - Unplugged, 1998; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - A Decade of Decay, 1996; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Susan Urban
    - Chords of Love, 1989; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Susan Urban; Professional Cassette
  - Sutton, Bill
    - Passing Through, Notes: Origin: Dodeka Records; Commercial CD 1 copy; Sutton, Bill; Dodeka Records (Box Box #03 (I))
      Sutton, Bill; Dodeka Records; Sutton, Bill; Dodeka Records; Commercial CD
    - Past Due, 1986; Notes: OCP-75 Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Sutton, Bill; Professional Cassette
    - Shake the Dust Off, 1989; Notes: D204 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_shake_the_dust_off; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
  - Sutton, Bill & Brenda
    - Bill & Brenda Sutton, The Incredible Bonus CD, Notes: Audio CD Origin: Bedlam House; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Sutton, Bill & Brenda; Bedlam House; Burnt CD
    - Owling at the Moon, 1994; Notes: DR-10010 Origin:; Professional Cassette 4 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Sutton, Bill & Brenda; Professional Cassette
  - Sutton, Bill and Brenda
    - And They Said it Wouldn't Last, 2016; Notes: Origin: Bedlam House Ltd.; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Sutton, Bill and Brenda; Bedlam House Ltd.; Professional CD
    - The Incredible Bonus CD, Notes: Signed by both Bill and Brenda Origin: Bedlam House; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Sutton, Bill and Brenda; Bedlam House; Professional CD
  - Sutton, Bill and Brenda (aka Bed and Breakfast)
    - Bill and Brenda Sutton Conclave 10/9/10 4:30 p.m. 65 minutes DATA DVD, 9 October 2010; Notes: Origin: Tim Ryan; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Sutton, Bill and Brenda (aka Bed and Breakfast); Tim Ryan; Burnt DVD
  - Sutton, Brenda Sinclair
    - Strangers No More, 1988; Notes: D205 Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Sutton, Brenda Sinclair; Professional Cassette
    - Strangers No More [home copy], 1988; Notes: Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Sutton, Brenda Sinclair; Tape
  - Swerdan, John
    - Startup Sounds: Songs about computers and technology sung and played by a human being, Notes: Dedicated to Lynn, signed by John Swerdan Origin: Slurry of Sounds Records SOS-001; Commercial CD 1 copy; Swerdan, John; Slurry of Sounds Records SOS-001 (Box Box #03 (I))
      Swerdan, John; Slurry of Sounds Records SOS-001; Swerdan, John; Slurry of Sounds Records SOS-001; Commercial CD
  - Syntax
    - Silent Planet, 1990; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Syntax; Professional Cassette
  - Tappan Sisters, The
    - When Teacher Wasn't Looking, 1993; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Tappan Sisters, The; Professional Cassette
  - Technical Difficulties
    - Please Stand By, 1988; Notes: Second Edition Origin: Bebop Productions, Rockville, MD: https://archive.org/details/filk_please_stand_by; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Technical Difficulties; Bebop Productions, Rockville, MD; Tape
    - Station Break, 1988; Notes: Origin: Fesarius Publications, Wakefield, MA: https://archive.org/details/filk_station_break; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Technical Difficulties; Fesarius Publications, Wakefield, MA; Tape
    - Please Stand By, 1986; Notes: Also at https://archive.org/details/lullabyforawearyworld Origin: Bebop Productions, Rockville, MD: https://archive.org/details/filk_please_stand_by; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
    - Please Stand By, 1986; Notes: one copy with slightly different liner notes Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_please_stand_by; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Technical Difficulties; Professional Cassette
    - Station Break, 1988; Notes: Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_station_break; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
    - Station Break 170, 1988; Notes: photocopy of official liner notes Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_station_break; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Technical Difficulties; Tape
  - Telynor
    - Telynor, 1987; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Telynor; Professional Cassette
    - Off the Beaten Track, 1992; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Tempest
    - Celtic Rock, 1989; Notes: Origin: Drone Studios, Redwood City, CA; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Tempest; Drone Studios, Redwood City, CA; Professional Cassette
    - Surfing to Mecca, 1994; Notes: FAM-10105-4 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Tempest; Professional Cassette
  - Terrifying Space Monkeys
    - Everyone's A Browncoat (In Their Own Way), 2009; Notes: for shindig purposes only Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy; Terrifying Space Monkeys; Produced by Zind at Swanky Bachelor Pad Studios Baltimore, Maryland (Box Box #06 (YY))
      Terrifying Space Monkeys; Produced by Zind at Swanky Bachelor Pad Studios Baltimore, Maryland; Terrifying Space Monkeys; Produced by Zind at Swanky Bachelor Pad Studios Baltimore, Maryland; Commercial CD
  - The Gazebo Singers
    - The Gazebo Singers, 1997; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      The Gazebo Singers; Professional Cassette
  - TheLoneGunman
    - Filk! by TheLoneGunman, Notes: Origin: Guitars are Guns Records; Commercial CD 1 copy; TheLoneGunman; Guitars are Guns Records (Box Box #05 (J))
      TheLoneGunman; Guitars are Guns Records; TheLoneGunman; Guitars are Guns Records; Commercial CD
  - This is SpaceRock
    - Born To Go, 1997; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      This is SpaceRock; Professional Cassette
  - Three Weird Sisters
    - Rite the First Time, Notes: Origin: Bedlam House, Ltd. www.bedlamhouse.com; Commercial CD 1 copy; Three Weird Sisters; Bedlam House, Ltd (Box Box #03 (I))
      Three Weird Sisters; Bedlam House, Ltd; Three Weird Sisters; Bedlam House, Ltd. www.bedlamhouse.com; Commercial CD
    - Third Thyme's the Charm, 13 February 2012; Notes: Promotional (burnt) version, signed by all four Weird Sisters, "Enjoy the Music, Harold!" Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Three Weird Sisters; Burnt CD
  - Thundering Asteroids
    - The Nerdpunk Guide to the Galaxy, 2014; Notes: Includes sticker and thank you note. Origin: Haywire Recording; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Thundering Asteroids; Haywire Recording; Professional CD
  - Timberwolf
    - In the Tall Pines, Notes: non-filk Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #25 (II))
      Timberwolf; Professional Cassette
  - Time Lines
    - Time Lines Takes Flight, Notes: Origin:; Tape - obvious copy 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Time Lines; Tape - obvious copy
    - Time Lines Takes Flight, Notes: Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Time Lines; Tape
  - Timelines
    - Flies by Night, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Timelines; Professional Cassette
    - Flights of Fantasy, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
  - Tingstad, Eric / Rumbel, Nancy
    - Legends, 1988; Notes: C-1022 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Tingstad, Eric / Rumbel, Nancy; Professional Cassette
  - Tinney, Betsy
    - Release the Cello!, 2014; Notes: Origin: Rabbit Feathers Media; Commercial DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Tinney, Betsy; Rabbit Feathers Media; Commercial DVD
    - Wyverns in the Winery and Other Flights of Fancy, 2017; Notes: Origin: Mystic Fig Studios; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Tinney, Betsy; Mystic Fig Studios; Commercial CD
    - Release the Cello!, 2013; Notes: Origin: Rabbit Feathers Media; Commercial DVD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
  - Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen
    - Lady Bear's Jumble, 2009; Notes: Origin: Purple Paw Press, MaryEllen Todd Cocrane METC.2327@yarhoo.com, recorded @Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Commercial CD 1 copy; Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; Purple Paw Press, MaryEllen Todd Cocrane METC.2327@yarhoo.com, recorded @Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire (Box Box #06 (YY))
      Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; Purple Paw Press, MaryEllen Todd Cocrane METC.2327@yarhoo.com, recorded @Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; Purple Paw Press, MaryEllen Todd Cocrane METC.2327@yarhoo.com, recorded @Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Commercial CD
    - Lady Bear's Baker's Dozen, Notes: Signed "To Harold, Much love & Thanks, Bear" Origin: recorded @ Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Commercial CD 1 copy; Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; recorded @ Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire (Box Box #06 (YY))
      Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; recorded @ Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Todd-Cocrane, MaryEllen; recorded @ Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; recorded @ Appleland Productions Bob Dick Engineer Extrodinaire; Commercial CD
  - Tricky Pixie
    - Tricky Pixie - Live! Soul Food Books Redmond, WA, 11 July 2007; Notes: A limited release of Tricky Pixie's first official concert Origin:; Limited Edition CD 1 copy; Tricky Pixie (Box Box #06 (YY))
      Tricky Pixie; Tricky Pixie; Limited Edition CD
    - Mythcreants, 2009; Notes: Extensive liner notes on the recording process Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy; Tricky Pixie (Box Box #06 (YY))
      Tricky Pixie; Tricky Pixie; Commercial CD
  - Triskelion
    - Gearbox, Notes: Origin: Jaranth Studios, Bedford, TX; CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Triskelion; Jaranth Studios, Bedford, TX; CD
  - Uffington Horse
    - Promotional Album, 2004; Notes: Origin: @2004 Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; Commercial CD 1 copy; Uffington Horse; @2004 Sea Fire Productions, Inc. (Box Box #03 (I))
      Uffington Horse; @2004 Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; Uffington Horse; @2004 Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; Commercial CD
  - Ulbrich, Carla
    - Totally Average Woman, 2015; Notes: Signed: To Harold, All the Best, Carla Ulbrich Origin: Romantic Devil Records; CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Ulbrich, Carla; Romantic Devil Records; CD
    - Carla Ulbrich, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Ulbrich, Carla; Professional Cassette
  - Uncle Bonsai
    - The Essential Uncle Bonsai, 1992; Notes: YT-10002 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Uncle Bonsai; Professional Cassette
  - Unknown Artist
    - Filk wavs: Rogow, Alive+Filking, Rogow, Alive+Filking Final, Roundworm, not used (DO NOT SHARE), Shrinkwrap blues, Songs posted to filk archive, Steve Goodman, The Wail from Down Under, Wolves and Changelings (edited), 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD
    - Filk wavs: Carmen Miranda's Ghost, Conclave @ Sweeny's Spasm 1 (edited), Let's Have a Filksing (edited, wavs), No Sheep Aloud (unused tracks), now - edited, OVFF 2001 Minidisc, 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk wavs, 1 April 2007; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk wavs, 1 August 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - NYC Housefilk 3rd Feb 2008 - Raw Recodings and Concom meeting, 3 February 2008; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD
    - James Blonde - May 2007 Housefilk - Kathy Sands Music audio only, 1 July 2007; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Do Hackers Dream of Electric Sheep, Session #2, Raw Recordings, 08-07, 1 August 2007; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - NYC Housefilk 9-17-06 - wav - unedited, 17 September 2006; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - NYC Housefilk 9-7-06 - Audacity files, 17 September 2006; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Housefilk NYC Raw Audacity Files 11-05-06, 5 November 2006; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Housefilk NYC Nov 5 2006 WAV Files Unedited, 5 November 2006; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Raw Filk - 2-07, 1 February 2007; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Raw Filk .wav - 2-07, 1 February 2007; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Eli - Filk MP3s Disc 3, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 2 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Eli - Filk MP3s Disc 1, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Eli - Filk MP3s Disc 2, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 17 - 1/06, 1 January 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 18 - 1/06, 1 January 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 15 - 1/06, 1 January 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 16 - 1/06, 1 January 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 19 - 2007 Update, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 4 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 19 - 2007 Update, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 6 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 8 - 7/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 9 - 7/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 7 - 7/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 3 - Revision .2 - 7/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 5 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 6 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 3 Revision 1.0 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 4 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk, Notes: Origin: Loose Filk MP3s; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Loose Filk MP3s; Burnt CD
    - Worldcon 2006 Filk, Albacon 2006 Recording, Kathy Sands Filk Recording Singing against the Wind #5, Notes: Origin: Various MP3s and scans; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Various MP3s and scans; Burnt DVD
    - Singing Against the Wind.wav Version 3 Tentative CD 7-06, 1 July 2006; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk WAVs 10/08, 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk WAVs 10/08, 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 5 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 6 - 01/04, 1 January 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 7 - 07/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Harold Stein - Filk MP3s - Disk 3 - Revision 2 - 07/04, 1 July 2004; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Vixy + Tony - July 11, 2008, 11 July 2008; Notes: Origin: Concert DVD; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Concert DVD; Burnt DVD
    - Christmas in Orbit - Copyright OCLS 2005, Notes: Liner Notes: Christmas in Orbit, Suzette Haden Eglen, Rebecca Haden, and Randy Farran Origin: Audio CD; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Audio CD; Burnt CD
    - Harry Chapin Concert Bootleg, Notes: Origin: Harry Chapin Concert Bootleg; Burnt CD 3 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Harry Chapin Concert Bootleg; Burnt CD
    - Philcon 2006, Raw recordings, Disc 2, Notes: Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Burnt DVD
    - Philcon 2006, Raw recordings, Disc 1, 11/06, 1 November 2006; Notes: Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Singing Against the Wind Session 4 Master Files uncleaned! - 7/01, Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Lover Art - Final tracks, all data - One Filk, Two Filk, Old Filk, New Filk, Master, unused tracks, data - 7/09, 1 July 2009; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Ad Astra MP3 files 7/03, 1 July 2003; Notes: Preliminary copy of album released as "To Touch the Stars" Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Burnt CD
    - Filk Songs and Weird Al Concert, 9-2-00, 2 September 2000; Notes: Possibly Harold's entire collection at the time Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk 2 - 10/02, 1 October 2002; Notes: Possibly Harold's entire collection at the time Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Raw Filk WAVs file 10/06, 1 October 2006; Notes: Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Again, Congenial Filk (+ edited), Concerto in A Filk Minor, Auditory Confusion, Mister Author, Chapin Tribute 1987, Raw Filk .wavs, 12/06, 1 December 2006; Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Alive and Filking - Raw Files; Dorothy Dridge Memorial, Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk WAVs 04/07, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Filk .WAVs, Notes: Origin: Rips of tapes + web materials; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Marvin Kittman - Audio Files, Notes: Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))